http://www.foodbankcny.org/privacy-policy/

Agency Training RSVP
Hunger Prevention and Nutrition Assistance Program (HPNAP)
Privacy Policy
Information Collection and UseWe may collect other non-personally identifiable information about your computer such as the type of browser you are using or the domain name of your Internet service provider.The Food Bank is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.How We Use the Information We CollectNon-personally identifiable information may be used in aggregate form to analyze the usage of our site and improve site design and interface. The information that we collect will not be disclosed to third parties unless in response to a legal claim or law enforcement agency's request.Aside from standard tracking data, the only other information we collect is data you knowingly provide through our online forms, which may include name, email address, address, telephone numbers, interests, and similar information. We do not and will not request or store personally identifying or sensitive information, such as credit card information or social security numbers.Food Bank of Central New York uses the information you voluntarily share with us in order to send requested electronic communications, printed publications or mail appeals or to help improve our website functionality. If you wish to do so, you may “opt out” of receiving any of our communications at any time.Donations We never sell, share or rent our supporters’ names or information collected from online or offline donations. Please refer to PayPal and Network For Good websites for more information on their respective privacy policies.CookiesCookies are small text files stored by your browser. Cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience of our site.As well as cookies, our website uses tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.LinksThis website contains links to other sites. The Food Bank is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which Food Bank of Central New York has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be differ from ours.FeedbackUsers may provide feedback to the Food Bank by sending an e-mail to infosys@foodbankcny.org. Any contact information entered when providing feedback will only be used to acknowledge or respond to that feedback.
© 2020 Food Bank of Central New York
Food Bank of Central New York is a 501(c)(3) not-for-profit organization.
EIN #22-2816988
Tax Exempt #191474
USDA Non-Discrimination Statement
